[{"answer": "Well, I'm a citizen of this country.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Does that sum up Michael Moore?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "FOX, right?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "People are always cynical at first whenever there's a movement for -- or a protest that's starting.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Not New Yorkers.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What kind of people are they?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, there's no -- I didn't meet any ex-bankers.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Are they -- what are they?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "I mean this is the wrong way for the American dream to work, isn't it?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I don't think it was a -- I don't know if it was a protest.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "What did you think of that protest?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "No -- no.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "There has to be -- there has to be a control over this, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Where is your line drawn in active protesting?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "No, no, of course not.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "You wouldn't endorse looting, would you?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "When you saw Obama's jobs plan come out, do you have any confidence it's gong to work?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Has he failed in not doing this before?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Who are the bad guys, do you think?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "But tell me this --", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "And we don't, right?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "No, we've asked him.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "And he's not going to come on and sit here and talk to you, right?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "You've got a company.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Is it really?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, there's nothing pure about capitalism.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Well -- isn't it in its purest sense?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "First of all, I do well.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Is there a good form of capitalism?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "It's like saying -- you know, when you say the word capitalism, you have to talk about it in its current sense.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Has it simply been corrupted?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "It went wrong because people -- first of all, we started rewarding people not for making things or inventing things.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Where did it go wrong?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "The first part of that -- I plead guilty to the dangerous part maybe.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Do you concede to either?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "I could tell you things that I agree with conservatives on.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Do you have any views that you think are genuinely surprising to people who just think you are a predictable knee-jerk liberal?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "At the very beginning there might have been some people who were trying to join the Tea Party to say some reasonable things because they were upset at Wall Street and what was happening, but these days, no, the Tea Party is a wing of the Republican Party thinking, it's funded by billionaires.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "I mean do you have a blanket distrust and hatred of all things Tea Party or can you recognize that some things they say are completely reasonable and that's why they gather support?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Well, I don't know but --", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Do you think CNN would do that?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I would have a debate with you tomorrow.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Well, how about a CNN/Teachers union debate?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I don't -- I don't know.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Why has he pissed it away?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, there's only one.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Who -- to you who was the least worrying Republican candidate?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Why isn't he getting the traction?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "No, sir, I've never struggled with that at all.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Have you struggled to sleep at night with the idea that any one of those might have been innocent?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Getting applause for defending Texas' record on capital punishment, which is -- you know, is it something worth applauding in the modern age, Michael?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "No, I don't think they do.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Do you think Americans know how few other countries actually have the death penalty?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "OORE: And I don't think they know where we stand in terms of how many people we execute.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Why don't you think they do?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "It should absolutely be the end of the debate.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "-- that to me is the end of the debate, isn't it?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "That's a good question.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "How do you change that thinking?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I would have done exactly what Obama did and use our special forces, who are some of our smartest and best trained soldiers, to begin the effort to track down Osama bin Laden and his lieutenants and bring them to justice.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "What would you have done?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I've been to Flint.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Would you be willing to come up with us and see what the situation is like in Flint for people?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I cannot come up to Flint, I'm sorry.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Could you come up to Flint with us?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Where did it come from?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "I would say vindicated, but I'm expecting that some people wouldn't agree, but I do.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Pretty well?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Do you have moments of, I don't want to do this any more?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Did you think you were going to die?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Right now, I could -- this show would suddenly belong to Nancy Grace.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "You could kill me with a piece of dental floss?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Janet Jackson bares a breast and CBS is fined God knows how much money and yet he can say that over the air and encourage the unhinged to harm me like that, and nothing happens.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Where are they?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "I just thought how can a guy who hosts a show call for literally want to kill somebody like you for expressing a political opinion?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "I begged my parents to go to the seminary.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "He was kicking me out.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "He wasn't wrong, was he?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "Well, of course, you could be -- you could be in favor of that way or in favor of men.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "No, I think I sort of -- puberty kicked in a little late on me, but it kicked in there.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Did you genuinely sit there one day and think, I either never have sex again or I have to stop my plan to be a priest?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "No, I don't have groupies.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 748, "question": "Do you have groupies?", "qSentId": 747}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "You have the love of a good woman?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "True love?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "Wow!", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "What has been the greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "You mean if I could do it again?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "Seven hundred fifty miles.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "How long was that drive?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "I drove 900 miles to Quebec City to see Bob Dylan and Joan Baez in concert because that was the closest place they were playing to Michigan on that tour.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 793, "question": "Do you accept you're slightly mad in that case?", "qSentId": 792}, {"answer": "Completely crackers.", "docId": "110926pmt", "aSentId": 799, "question": "Go see David Letterman, 750 miles?", "qSentId": 798}]